chillopedia.com 2017-02-15

# Privacy Policy

At **Chillopedia.com** , we recognize that privacy of your personal information is important. As with most other websites, we collect the data you provide to us when you visit or post a comment to our site. This information may include your name, your email address, your city,your IP address, your ISP, the browser you used to visit our site (such as Internet Explorer, Chrome, Safari or Firefox etc), the times you visited our site, the time you spent on our site and which pages you visited throughout our site.

Your personal information will **never** be released, sold, or rented to any entities or individuals outside **  Chillopedia.com** under any circumstance.

### **Log Files**

Like many other Web sites, **Chillopedia.com** makes use of log files. The information inside the log files includes internet protocol ( IP ) addresses, type of browser, Internet Service Provider ( ISP ), date/time stamp, referring/exit pages, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track user’s movement around the site, and gather demographic information. IP addresses, and other such information are not linked to any information that is personally identifiable.

### **Cookies & 3rd Party Advertisements**

Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on our site. Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to our users based on their visit to our site (and on other sites present in Adsense’s Publisher network). You may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the [Google ad and content network privacy policy](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html).

We allow third-party companies to serve ads and/or collect certain anonymous information when you visit our website. These companies may use non-personally identifiable information (e.g., click stream information, browser type, time and date, subject of advertisements clicked or scrolled over) during your visits to this and other websites that are part of Google’s Adsense for Publishers program in order to provide advertisements about goods and services likely to be of greater interest to you.

**Chillopedia.com** has no access to or control over these cookies that are used by third-party advertisers. These companies typically use a cookie or third party web beacon to collect this information. To learn more about this behavioral advertising practice or to opt-out of this type of advertising, you can visit [this link](http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp).

### Links To Other Sites

Our Site may contain links to other sites that are not operated by us. If you click on a third party link, you will be directed to that third party’s site. We strongly advise you to review the Privacy Policy of every site you visit.

**Chillopedia.com** has no control over, and assumes no responsibility for, the content, privacy policies, or practices of any third party sites or services.

### Changes To This Privacy Policy

**Chillopedia.com**  may update this Privacy Policy from time to time. We will notify you of any changes by posting the new Privacy Policy on the Site. You are advised to review this Privacy Policy periodically for any changes.

### **Further Information**

If you require any more information or have any questions about our privacy policy, please feel free to [contact us](https://chillopedia.com/contact-us/).
